# JEREMY WU

0421 128 153 | wu jeremy94@outlook.com | Sydney, New South Wales

# Graduate Bachelor of Business | Major in Human Resource Management | Minor in Business Law

## **BIOGRAPHY | CAREER GOAL**

Currently seeking a fulltime position a reputable Melbourne, Sydney or Brisbane employer, were I can establish my career and enhance my current skill set.

Raised on the Sunshine Coast and attending school locally at Immanuel Lutheran College from pre-school through to graduation, I am a 25 year old seeking a graduate level opportunity in Business or Human Resource Management as a way to initiate my professional career. I recently completed my Bachelor of Business, Majoring in Human Resources Management, and achieving a Minor in Business Law from the University of the Sunshine Coast as of November 2016. I have 7 years of work experience and management roles in two family businesses.

#### **EDUCATION**

### **Bachelor of Business | Major in Human Resource Management**

2017

University of the Sunshine Coast 2012 - 2016 (Graduation ceremony in March 2017) Completed my studies at the University of the Sunshine Coast with a Bachelor of Business, majoring in Human Resources Management and minoring in Business Law.

# Certificate II in Business Certificate II in Information Technology

2011 2010

Sunshine Coast Institute of Tafe

# **Year 12 High school Certificate**

1999 - 2011

Immanuel Lutheran College

#### **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

#### **Kawana Chinese Restaurant**

2010 - 2016

Started by my father in 1989, Kawana Chinese Restaurant is an authentic family run Chinese dine in and takeaway restaurant located in Kawana Waters, Queensland. I worked here from a young age, but started taking on more responsibility in 2010. My roles were customer service, kitchen hand and training and managing other employees. Serving the local community for over 27 years, I learnt a great deal about business operations, staff training, work ethics and customer service from my family.

Ink Brothers 2013 – 2019

Started by my brother and I in 2013. Ink Brothers is a retail store that sells printer cartridges and also does design and promotional products. My roles was the store manager which consisted which day to day operation of the store, working with clientele and also training employees.

#### PERSONAL ATTRIBUTES

- Effective Communication Skills: I believe I articulate and communicate my thoughts well to others, especially in professional environments and when working with other team members or customers.
- Honest and reliable: I have strong morals and ethics. I believe I am honest, reliable and responsible.

- Flexible: I understand the need for flexibility, and realise last-minute demands and changes may occur in a workplace. I am comfortable with changing environments and situations and can be adaptable at all times.
- Time Management: I can effectively prioritise and manage my time by allocating tasks by priority and create lists and systems to manage my time well.

### **REFEREES**

#### Jacinta O'Brien

Community Relations Officer, Red Cross Blood Service Character Reference 0407 392 365

#### Jon Wu

Ink Brothers Manager 0401236011

#### Josh Kent

Personal Reference - childhood/school friend 0411 196 617 | j kento@hotmail.com